Hello there!
We're losing our dungeon?
So much for guard duty.
That maniac fused the
Stratum Lords together.
I'm guessing they're on their
way to the fortified city.
Fly if you have wings, and
run if you're fleet-footed!
Tell the Empire and nearby towns
and villages what's coming?
You got it!
We intend to follow them,
but what about your group?
You can count on us to take
down some monster scum.
Least we can do to pay Boxo
back for his sacrifice!
Yes.
We'll gladly risk our
lives to aid the cause.
We've got to do this.
Otherwise, we forfeit our man cards.
You in, bro? You know it.
I'll do anything.
I can't let a box be more manly than me.
We must buy some time.
For the sake of Boxo.
I'd like to stay by your side.
I'm aware I can't atone
for my prior villainy.
I'll go with you.
Personally speaking, I don't think
I'll ever truly forgive them.
I'll stay behind and help dig
up Boxo. Pity, too. I'll...
I'll help...
from here.
I'm staying put.
Will want to use my magic
items to help with the digging.
Nothing would please me more than to
help rescue our valiant master, Boxxo.
Alas, I'm certain if I don't turn
my blade to slaying monsters,
he'll be angry with me.
So I tearfully trust this task to you.
That leaves Lamas.
But I don't even need to ask.
The whole thing is unbearable.
But every last one of us knows
he's still alive out there.
On the outside, I'm just a big metal box.
But inside, I've still got a human soul.
In this new world of wonders,
I travel to and fro on the back of
my super strong partner, Llamas.
The name's Boxxo. Hello there.
That means yes, by the way!
Ashtray, baby, to all
so hot, chill, like you.
I got to hit by my head and
it's time to get over to me.
I'm so afraid, if not, I'll fight.
It's so afraid.
I'm so afraid.
I'm afraid, we're doing the best time.
We've already overtaken
the monster's army.
The Akar's speed never ceases to amaze me.
Indeed.
And it's a good omen that
it hasn't disappeared.
That would seem to suggest that our
friend Boxo is still in one piece.
What of the surface?
I hope my sister is unharmed.
We're really hauling it.
Won't take long to reach
the fortified city.
Maybe a week tops?
But since we can't risk entering
the aptly named Murderous Forest,
we'll have to go around.
Meanwhile,
our foes will undoubtedly cut through
with that enormous beast leading the way.
I know.
I'll charge into the Murderous
Forest and keep the dastards busy.
With luck, that'll buy
us the time we need.
That kind of idea's a death wish.
Are you so eager to lose your life?
No, I'll never die.
It would displease
Master Boxo if I did so.
I guess there's no getting through to him.
Swear to me on Boxo's honor
that you'll return to our ranks,
still alive and kicking. I swear.
Then you better get to it.
Remember to value your
life above all else.
I second the motion.
Living is vastly preferable to dying.
Cherish your life along
with your boots. I shall.
Try not to die.
If things get hairy, make a run for it.
Only cowards lurk in the shadows.
I find it exhilarating that
you can sense my presence.
Who are you?
Good question.
I don't recall what my name was
before I was a bag of bones.
It doesn't matter anymore, as I
now answered a four-finger general.
I didn't expect to find one
of the five-finger generals.
I'm curious.
They say only a master
swordsman could have cut
through the bars of the
pinky general's cell.
Are you the one to blame?
Guilty.
I was called in to clean
up the mess she had made.
Oh, what joy! What bliss!
It's been an eternity since
someone blocked by opening strike.
This should be quite amusing.
We're running the right way, right?
Right.
Just keep running.
The map said the next town's at
the foot of that little mountain,
so that's where we're going!
We'd better hurry! Oh, wow! Drillworthy!
The village and the veggies are abandoned.
I'm not even a salad gal, but those greens
are calling my name and I'm listening!
Who would have thought something could
smell healthy and yummy at the same time?
Can we stuff our faces now?
Yeah, but let's try not to eat at all.
I bet other animals want in on it too.
Well, let's dive in!
It's eight o 'clock!
A new experience!
It's all juicy and splashes
around in my mouth when I bite it!
Plus, it has a rich
flavor losing with umami!
I don't believe it! I can't!
I need to know what these
delicious veggies I think are!
Imagine combining these veggies
with the whole lot of fried chicken!
I like these veggies even better
than the ones from Kikuyu.
Though they kind of remind me of
her stock when I think about it.
Wonder what that's about.
He's good.
I doubt I'll be able to best him.
But I must.
I cannot allow this enemy to roam free.
lest the friends I left behind
pay dearly for my failure.
I must end this battle here and now.
Interesting.
You're aware my skills surpass your
own, yet you refuse to back down.
I have my reasons for standing strong.
Well, how fortuitous.
I had grown weary of cutting down
opponents as they flee in terror.
Forgive me, Master Boxo.
It seems I'm destined to
meet my end here. And yet,
even as my life slips away from me,
I swear to give this final
battle everything I've got.
well now a commendable last-ditch effort
i accept this fascinating challenge
An Essig?
Unbelievable.
Usaka! Usarion!
Usarion! Usabi!
Keep our enemy distracted
as long as you can!
Good sir, please hurry!
Now's your chance to make a run for it!
Kayaichi? Nishwa?
Is that really you?
We'll have to exchange stories later.
For the time being, our top
priority is defeating this guy.
Agreed.
If you're open to suggestions,
may I ask that you instruct the
Essex to continue distracting him?
As you wish.
Hey, Usata!
Keep whittling away at the enemy!
Truly a valiant effort, Mishuel.
You've come so far.
In truth, I would have been
doomed were it not for the Essex.
Did you hear that, my furry friends?
Allow me to introduce you, Mishuel.
This is Usata, the head of the family.
The elegant damsel next to him with
the beautiful fluffy coat is Usarion.
And the tiny versions of them are
their children, Usarion and Usapi.
How is it that I had no idea you
were an animal trainer, sister?
And they're rather powerful.
I'm not an animal trainer.
These little fuzzballs
are my friends and allies.
I see.
By the way, what are you doing
in such a dangerous place?
I could ask the same of you.
You are the eighth princess
of this land, after all.
As there is much to share, I
suggest an exchange of information.
Rest, Amos.
You've been working yourself to the bone.
You can't help Boxxo if you
keel over dead from exhaustion.
She's right.
You know Boxxo would be mad
if he could see you like this.
Rest!
When Bokso's buried in the dirt!
I understand.
That all makes complete sense.
As for me,
I came from the Fortified City when we
caught wind something
was amiss in the forest.
The matter of the Guardian
had only just been
settled when the dungeon
met with that untimely fate.
The Guardian?
Of the Fortified City.
He left us to fight the Demon
Lord, but he was badly injured.
It was only recently that we
learned of his whereabouts.
He was able to recover just the other day.
I didn't know such a person existed.
I've been in the dungeon a good while,
so forgive me for being
behind on current events.
Mishuel,
it's been a long time since I heard any
news about you and I've been worried sick.
That whole time, you were in the dungeon?
Tell me everything about your new master.
Where to start?
His heart is most sincere and generous.
He keeps a calm demeanor no matter
how treacherous the situation.
He protects and cares for his friends.
The Guardian sounds extremely commendable,
but Master Boxxo is utterly magnificent.
Still your tongue!
Though I'll admit Boxxo
sounds extraordinary,
you would be remiss to suggest that he
could possibly surpass the Guardian.
I must beg your pardon.
It wasn't my intention to
belittle him, I swear. Still,
the truth remains that
there isn't a person in
the world who holds a
candle to Master Boxxo.
Not so fast!
The Guardian is most generous and
open-minded, truly a being without evil.
Actually, you don't know what
Master Boxxo is capable of.
Perhaps we should save this lively
debate for when our work is finished.
Agreed.
If we're unable to slow down
the monster army here and now,
I fear the fortified city
will very soon be overrun.
With your friends notifying the city
dwellers, there's no cause for concern.
But just to be safe, I'll
help you set some traps.
With Usata and the others here,
we can even process timber.
I'll make you proud, Master.
You'll see.
I'll distract the fiends without delay and
buy enough time for you
to join us in battle.
Boxo. Boxo.
Boxo!
It appears we'll reach the fortified
city sooner than we thought.
Also, I wasn't expecting to behold
such abundant farmland here.
The city has recently become
renowned for its agriculture.
I hear the impeccable quality of their
vegetables as the talk of the Empire.
The city's lord must be a
rather shrewd businessperson.
Is there anything useful you can
tell us about them, Director?
Of course there is.
They say she's beautiful and succeeded
her father at a young age a few years ago.
Oh, and also, this one's important.
It's best to avoid eye contact.
I hear it's especially
risky for human males.
Don't be ridiculous.
You make it sound like we'll fall in
love the moment we lock eyes with her.
Your wait is over.
The lady has arrived and we'll see you.
I'm sorry for keeping you waiting.
My name is Jessica, and as the
ruling lady, I welcome all of you.
I think we finally met our match.
I already have a girlfriend.
I can't remember her name,
but I know she exists.
Pull it together? I have.
Those shoes were orgasmic.
My feelings for Lady Jessica have
reached their climax and been expelled.
Please, young master.
Please, m 'lady.
It's important that you stop spreading
your charm so indiscriminately,
as it's causing problems again.
I completely agree with Master Stuck.
Those eyes can turn
honest men into porndogs.
So it's best for everyone
if you keep them closed.
I see.
So we're dealing with the
forces of the Netherlord,
or rather the Left-Armed General,
despite our negotiations
with the Demon Lord's forces.
I beg your pardon, but what
negotiations are you referring to?
Currently, we're trying
to negotiate an armistice.
We've been working on it
with the Demon Lord's forces.
It seemed like we were
making considerable progress.
Lady Jessica,
the Left-Armed General has earned quite
the reputation as a no-good schemer.
Meaning he was trying to seize power.
My dear Steck,
please send a messenger to
the Demon Lord's territory and
let us hope the Guardian returns
before the enemy reaches us.
Motor, explain the situation
to our soldiers and citizens.
If that is what you wish,
then consider it done.
I'll take care of everything.
You must be exhausted
after your long journey.
Give me just a moment to
arrange lodging for you.
In the meantime,
please help yourself to some fresh
vegetables harvested from our land.
Those are the tastiest-looking
vegetables I've ever seen!
I know.
I'm literally drooling like an animal.
Such a delightful feast is worthy
of my full attention. True.
It's life-changing!
That's the ticket!
We'll just keep on whittling
them down from the rear!
I'll use my magic.
I'll join you!
She mixed magic with her daughter-in-law.
That was brutal.
What are you jabbering on about?
He called me his daughter-in-law?
Um, Big Sasori? Yes,
Kai? What's the matter?
Don't worry about it.
This world is too cruel!
Kai stole all the Lady
Killer genes from himself!
He really did, but it's okay.
When Boxo's back, we'll guilt him
into teaching us how to up our game!
Now you're speaking my language!
I hope they're already digging
him out and dusting him off.
We owe the big luck big
time for what he did.
Most certainly.
And it's high time we paid back our debt.
Let's start by mopping up some monsters!
We've got your back over here!
Let's show them how it's done!
Our hungry little spears
will dine on monster blood!
The star attraction has arrived!
You trainers are in for
a special treat today.
I'm sure you're already aware
I'm the shouting songstress.
In other words, the terrifying and
titillating Pinky General Kai rings.
And I'm here to make sure every
one of you suffers and dies.
I'm told you were captured
but managed to escape.
Sulream, it feels like it's been forever.
But I never liked you
anyway, so no harm, no foul.
Now I have the pleasure of personally
killing the Ring Finger General?
I must admit, it's a dream control!
I think the corpses are
combining! That's nasty!
This is quite absurd.
Could someone please
explain what's happening?
She's a necromancer, and
she's in her element.
As you can see,
a delicious assortment of monsters and
humans were tragically buried alive,
swallowed by a nasty landslide.
Impressed yet?
I call this my army of rot, stitched
together from fugitive corpses.
Because how freaking metal is that how
cute you came to play that makes this easy?
It means I don't have to hold back.
You see that I was able
to resist your pathetic?
attack.
You're playing it cool, but it's an act.
Got the theatrics, babe, cause I know
that last attempt must have
drained a crap ton of honor.
Now I finally get to jump on
that smug little face.
Let's make this chick bleed.
Now die.
This is no time to nap.
Keep Why the hell are you flopping around?
Hey, what's the meaning of this?
Why are your arms and legs turning to you?
Forgive me.
I'm the one who's responsible.
That's not fair!
Since when does a kid have wings?
And how the hell did you decay my army?
When the dungeon master set about removing
my blessing of decay, I made a request.
I wish to be able to use it at will
instead of losing it completely.
You're talking out of your butt!
Though if you say you're the one
to blame, I'll have to kill you!
Is that right?
You think I'd let you kill my boy?
Now's as good a time as any to show off!
This crazy lady was just our opening act!
That's one obstacle
down, but it's not over.
She looks pretty miffed.
It's going to be hard to get her to
understand why I kept this from her.
If we're running low, I'll
chop some more wood for us.
If anyone's backing muscle,
come help me lift something.
I'll put whatever you want on
your tab, so eat your fill.
You're so generous.
Munami, you have work to do.
Are you happy?
It was worth it, even though it was
a risk bringing all that seasoning.
Yep, you're the best, Mom.
Miss Lori will be ready to depart shortly.
Let me know when we're good to go.
We'll leave as soon as
my things are loaded.
About that.
The monsters that emerge from the
dungeon might still be present.
That said, it's far too dangerous
to leave without a hunter escort.
We'll need every ounce of
manpower to rebuild this place,
which means we'll just
have to manage on our own.
And besides, I have the utmost faith in
everyone we've entrusted with our lives.
Though really,
this will undoubtedly be wasted effort
when Boxo inevitably returns to us.
Ladies, I can't offer
any work for a spell.
So if you wish to profit, you
should move to another town.
Does this mean you're staying?
But the only pounding to do
here is with hammers and nails.
Miss Shirley, we still
owe you for taking us in.
We'll follow wherever you lead us.
I'm sure there isn't a better
boss in the entire world.
Such silliness.
But sure, I'll take it.
We'll rebuild.
Then resume our good work,
draining lonely men of money.
That's our Lamas.
It's clear you'll never
change, no matter what.
He's still alive!
I gotta hurry and save him
before he isn't anymore!
Save the speech.
You know I'm not going to stop you from
searching, but I won't let you go overboard.
Okay.
See this?
It's a magic item that probes for souls.
Does it dig?
It won't help with labor, but it's possible
it can help us locate Bokso's soul.
Hello there!
I love my story.
I love your story.
I look forward to serving you again.